{"0": {"Question": "what is identical to \"logistics\"?", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "1": {"Question": "what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"? (hint: what is identical to \"logistics\"?)", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "2": {"Question": "what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "3": {"Question": "what is identical to \"logistics\"? (hint: what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?)", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "4": {"Question": "\"processor\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "5": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" is part of ____? (hint: \"processor\" is part of ____?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "6": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "7": {"Question": "\"processor\" is part of ____? (hint: \"flash memory\" is part of ____?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "8": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "9": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"information can change\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "10": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?, what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "11": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?, what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?, what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "12": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?, what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "13": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?, what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?, what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "14": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "15": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"? (hint: what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?)", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "16": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "17": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "18": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "19": {"Question": "\"rfid tag\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "20": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is part of ____? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is part of ____?)", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "21": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "22": {"Question": "\"rfid tag\" is part of ____? (hint: \"barcode\" is part of ____?)", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "23": {"Question": "in the setting of \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\", what example does \"logistics\" have? (hint: \"logistics\" is identical to \"tracking things\")", "Answer": "Walmart", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "24": {"Question": "\"Walmart\" is an example of \"logistics\". (hint: \"logistics\" is identical to \"tracking things\")", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "25": {"Question": "what is identical to \"logistics\"?", "Answer": "Tracking things", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "26": {"Question": "in the setting of \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\", what example does \"logistics\" have? (hint: what is identical to \"logistics\"?)", "Answer": "Walmart", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "27": {"Question": "\"Walmart\" is an example of \"logistics\". (hint: what is identical to \"logistics\"?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "28": {"Question": "what is identical to \"tracking things\"?", "Answer": "logistics", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "29": {"Question": "\"logistics\" is not identical to \"Tracking things\".", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "30": {"Question": "in the setting of \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\", what example does \"logistics\" have?", "Answer": "Walmart", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "31": {"Question": "in the setting of \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\", \"walmart\" is an example of _____?", "Answer": "logistics", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "32": {"Question": "\"logistics\". is an example of \"Walmart\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "33": {"Question": "what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"? (hint: \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is identical to \"logistics\")", "Answer": "moving place to place in a certain time frame", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "34": {"Question": "\"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". (hint: \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is identical to \"logistics\")", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "35": {"Question": "what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"?", "Answer": "logistics", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "36": {"Question": "what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"? (hint: what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"?)", "Answer": "moving place to place in a certain time frame", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "37": {"Question": "\"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". (hint: what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "38": {"Question": "what is identical to \"logistics\"?", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "39": {"Question": "\"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is identical to \"logistics\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "40": {"Question": "what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"?", "Answer": "moving place to place in a certain time frame", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "41": {"Question": "what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "42": {"Question": "\"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\" is not identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\".", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "43": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". (hint: \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\" is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\")", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "44": {"Question": "\"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". is used for \"barcode\" (hint: \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\" is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\")", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "45": {"Question": "what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?", "Answer": "move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "46": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". (hint: what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?)", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "47": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is used for \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". (hint: what is identical to \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\"?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "48": {"Question": "what is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\"?", "Answer": "moving place to place in a certain time frame", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "49": {"Question": "\"moving place to place in a certain time frame\" is identical to \"move lots of things between different places on a certain time scale\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "50": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"moving place to place in a certain time frame\".", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "51": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is used for _____", "Answer": "moving place to place in a certain time frame", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "52": {"Question": "\"moving place to place in a certain time frame\". is used for \"barcode\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "53": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"can easily be networked\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "54": {"Question": "\"be within proximity\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"can easily be networked\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "55": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "56": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "57": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "58": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "59": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "60": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"flash memory\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "61": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "62": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\". is a part of \"flash memory\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "63": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "64": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "65": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "66": {"Question": "\"be within proximity\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\"., \"information can change\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "67": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "information can change", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "68": {"Question": "\"information can change\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "69": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "70": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" is a part of \"RFID tag\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "71": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "72": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "73": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 1}, "74": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\"., \"a lot more information\" has attribute of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 1}, "75": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "a lot more information", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "76": {"Question": "\"a lot more information\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "77": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "information can change", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "78": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"information can change\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "79": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "80": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\". is a part of \"flash memory\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "81": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "82": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "83": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "84": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\"., \"processor\" is a part of \"rfid tag\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "85": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "processor", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "86": {"Question": "\"processor\" is a part of \"RFID tag\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "87": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "a lot more information", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "88": {"Question": "\"a lot more information\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\" (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "89": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "information can change", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "90": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"information can change\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "91": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "92": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" is a part of \"RFID tag\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "93": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "94": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "95": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "96": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is compared to \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "97": {"Question": "_____ is comparable to \"rfid tag\".", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "98": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is comparable to _____", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "99": {"Question": "\"gets changed and updated over time\". has an attribute of \"flash memory\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "100": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"?", "Answer": "processor", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "101": {"Question": "\"processor\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "102": {"Question": "\"processor\" is a part of \"RFID tag\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "103": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?", "Answer": "a lot more information", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "104": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"a lot more information\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "105": {"Question": "\"a lot more information\". has an attribute of \"RFID tag\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "106": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?", "Answer": "information can change", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "107": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"information can change\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "108": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"information can change\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "109": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"rfid tag\"?", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "110": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "111": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\". is a part of \"flash memory\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "112": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?", "Answer": "can easily be networked", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "113": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"can easily be networked\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "114": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"can easily be networked\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "115": {"Question": "what attribute does \"rfid tag\" have?", "Answer": "be within proximity", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "116": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"be within proximity\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "117": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" has an attribute of \"be within proximity\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "118": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"barcode\". (hint: \"never change\" has attribute of \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "scanner", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "119": {"Question": "\"scanner\" is used for \"barcode\". (hint: \"never change\" has attribute of \"barcode\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "120": {"Question": "what attribute does \"barcode\" have?", "Answer": "never change", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "121": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"barcode\". (hint: what attribute does \"barcode\" have?)", "Answer": "scanner", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "122": {"Question": "\"scanner\" is used for \"barcode\". (hint: what attribute does \"barcode\" have?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "123": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"never change\"?", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "124": {"Question": "\"barcode\" has an attribute of \"never change\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "125": {"Question": "_____ is used for \"barcode\".", "Answer": "scanner", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "126": {"Question": "\"scanner\" is used for _____", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "127": {"Question": "\"barcode\". is used for \"scanner\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "128": {"Question": "what is identical to \"device\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\"., \"barcode\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "box", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "129": {"Question": "\"device\" is identical to \"box\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\"., \"barcode\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "130": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"device\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "131": {"Question": "what is identical to \"device\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\"., _____ is part of \"device\"?)", "Answer": "box", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "132": {"Question": "\"device\" is identical to \"box\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\"., _____ is part of \"device\"?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "133": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is a part of \"device\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "134": {"Question": "what is identical to \"device\"? (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "box", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "135": {"Question": "\"device\" is identical to \"box\". (hint: \"rfid tag\" is a part of \"device\".)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "136": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"device\"?", "Answer": "RFID tag", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "137": {"Question": "\"rfid tag\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "138": {"Question": "\"RFID tag\" is a part of \"device\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "139": {"Question": "_____ is part of \"device\"?", "Answer": "barcode", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "140": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is part of ____?", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "141": {"Question": "\"barcode\" is a part of \"device\".", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "142": {"Question": "what is identical to \"device\"?", "Answer": "box", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "143": {"Question": "what is identical to \"box\"?", "Answer": "device", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "144": {"Question": "\"device\" is not identical to \"box\".", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "145": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" causes _____? (hint: \"gets changed and updated over time\" has attribute of \"flash memory\".)", "Answer": "see the whole path that the box took", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "146": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" causes _____?", "Answer": "see the whole path that the box took", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "147": {"Question": "what attribute does \"flash memory\" have?", "Answer": "gets changed and updated over time", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "148": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" causes _____? (hint: what attribute does \"flash memory\" have?)", "Answer": "see the whole path that the box took", "Type": 1, "Level": 2}, "149": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" causes \"see the whole path that the box took\" (hint: what attribute does \"flash memory\" have?)", "Answer": "true", "Type": 0, "Level": 2}, "150": {"Question": "what has the attribute of \"gets changed and updated over time\"?", "Answer": "flash memory", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}, "151": {"Question": "\"gets changed and updated over time\". has an attribute of \"flash memory\"", "Answer": "false", "Type": 0, "Level": 3}, "152": {"Question": "\"flash memory\" causes _____?", "Answer": "see the whole path that the box took", "Type": 1, "Level": 3}}